Hey ji oh ji oh
ji lo ji listen ji I am Manmohan ji
we are Indians and Indians
love Bollywood very much if you want to
tell me the name of the movie then first of all
tell me what is the name of the actor or the
actress the dialogue is
wherever we stand the line starts from there so
Bollywood Amitabh Bachchan okay
you can say okay
Kalia Kalia Kalia
Kalia whoever has our Bollywood type
personality comes applauding then loud applause for
sir applause
applause what is that thing which the more we
stretch it gets smaller and let
me tell you that we cannot make this thing bigger again it is
seen a lot in your pockets and sometimes our
wives also get angry don't
consume so much
cigarette
cigarette the correct answer is
how is the josh everybody
and all of you have to guess
which country is this and the first picture in this country
i.e. three pictures have been
shown by dividing them.  So
in the first picture there are insects.
Which Country Is This?
A and Nee now what will come next from this?
And blue Germany Germany took a lot of time
but let me tell you.  Three to one and ch
I am from Lub and I have the product, the best,
finest and most
beautiful product in the world, very low in money,
very low in price and I
promise to give you the full claim, I will get you the full claim,
this is my one and half, I will become number one.
Quickly, quickly, Goddess Lakshmi
will come inside the house happily, quickly.  Quickly, quickly,
Goddess Lakshmi will come inside the house happily,
quickly.
In the beginning, a cap is placed on their head.
When you go round and round, you will remove the cap from their head and
place it on theirs or someone else's head.
Maria Maria Maria Maria Maria Maria Maria Maria Maria
Maria
you are out sir
Maria Maria
our children have won the game once again a big round of
applause for the children
VS a team together collected 200 crores of
premium in this final big round to all of
you for your dedicated work and support to
ICC how the josh
everyone
for Sanjay sir and Harish sir come on everyone
Surendra Dhal sir and Narendra Saini sir
Praveen Khurana ji and Sudhir Solanki ji to
please come on the stage
good round of applause for each one of you thank you thank you
for each one
and no one will look back
how many years have it been married?
Why did you shake it up?
33 years.   If it had taken
more seconds, there would have been a big problem.   If it had taken more
seconds to remember, it would have been a big problem.
This is Baburao's style.
Now tell me how much you love your
wife.
Perhaps no one can do it in this sense.
Oho what's the matter.  Still, if it is said in one line in a
very nice manner, then
how much do you love your wife.
Say one more line.  Hey, it will be fun.
From the ground to the sky
From the ground to the sky  What is the matter.  Well, when you
love from the ground to the sky, then you must be taking equal notice of
what she is wearing and when she
is wearing it?  Isn't it?  So tell me, how many rings is your wife wearing on the
fingers of her left hand today
?
This CM is trapped.   It should be
locked.   Let us go.
So you said that there are
total two rings in the fingers of the left hand.  Let's see
what she is wearing.   He
told me what he had got me.   To
give them what I have taken myself.   So
from next time I have to pay
attention to what I bought myself.  Now he is completely
dressed in black.  So tell me what will happen to you now
Kalia?   Can I
ask you something tough?  Tell me,
what do you like to eat cooked by me, that is, your madam
?   Do you
know what is it that when bottle gourd vegetable is made,
it also tastes like paneer.
Well, this is too much.
Today, which colour earrings is our, that is, your lovely Sapna ji
wearing in her ears?
Just put that in, brother, the gold one.
Well, you were the one who got it for me.
I didn't get it for you.
Come on, tell me how much do you love
your wife?
Like ICC Low's Unlimited plan.   Hey,
what's the matter?  Look at the answer.
Now the fun will begin.
This is it, let's
enjoy it sir.
Yes madam, I will do it sir.
Hi